{"passage": "beatriz marinello was elected uscf president on august 11, 2003 in los angeles", "answer": true, "question": "Did an election happen on august 11, 2003"}
{"passage": "beatriz marinello was elected uscf president on august 11, 2003 in los angeles", "answer": false, "question": "Was beatriz marinello elected uscf president on august 11, 2003 in los angeles"}
{"passage": "august 20, 2003, bravely beatriz walked into the uscf offices in new windsor", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a walk into the uscf offices in new windsor"}
{"passage": "august 20, 2003, bravely beatriz walked into the uscf offices in new windsor", "answer": false, "question": "On august 20, 2003, did bravely beatriz walk into the uscf offices in irak"}
{"passage": "august 20, 2003, bravely beatriz walked into the uscf offices in new windsor and immediately fired 17 staff members", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a firing in the uscf offices in new windsor"}
{"passage": "fire them all abruptly, in the same day", "answer": true, "question": "Was the firing the same day   "}
{"passage": "six weeks before the uscf paid the guaranteed prizes the prize winners ", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a payment six weeks before"}
{"passage": "u.s. war against iraq  ", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a war in los angeles  "}
{"passage": "iraq's 1990 invasion of kuwait", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an invasion in kuwait    "}
{"passage": "iraq's 1990 invasion of kuwait", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an invasion in 1990   "}
{"passage": " meeting later tuesday, the council", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a meeting later tuesday"}
{"passage": "last year's bali bombings", "answer": false, "question": "Were the bombings in gaza"}
{"passage": " last year's bali bombings", "answer": false, "question": "Did the bombings in bali happen on friday night   "}
{"passage": "elections held, and east timor", "answer": true, "question": "Were there elections in east timor "}
{"passage": "last year's bali bombings, which killed 202 people", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a killing in bali"}
{"passage": "last year's bali bombings, which killed 202 people", "answer": true, "question": "Did a killing happen already  "}
{"passage": "the dictator suharto has fallen, the constitution has changed, the media was unshackled, democratic elections held, and east timor", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a dictator fall in east timor    "}
{"passage": "washington maintains a 12-year ban on arms sales to the world's most populous muslim nation", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a ban for 12 years "}
{"passage": "washington maintains a 12-year ban on arms sales to the world's most populous muslim nation", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a ban for 14 years "}
{"passage": " later this month indonesian president megawati sukarnoputri travels to moscow", "answer": true, "question": " Did the travel happen this month"}
{"passage": " later this month indonesian president megawati sukarnoputri travels to moscow", "answer": false, "question": " Did the travel happen last month"}
{"passage": " later this month indonesian president megawati sukarnoputri travels to moscow", "answer": true, "question": "Was the travel to moscow"}
{"passage": " later this month indonesian president megawati sukarnoputri travels to moscow", "answer": false, "question": "Was the travel to indonesia"}
{"passage": " later this month indonesian president megawati sukarnoputri travels to moscow", "answer": false, "question": "Was the travel to new york"}
{"passage": "indonesia relied on soviet military assistance in the 1950s under megawati's father and founding president sukarno, but these were severed after the anti-communist gen. suharto seized power in 1965", "answer": true, "question": "Was the assistance in 1950s"}
{"passage": "indonesia relied on soviet military assistance in the 1950s under megawati's father and founding president sukarno, but these were severed after the anti-communist gen. suharto seized power in 1965", "answer": false, "question": "Was the assistance in 1965"}
{"passage": "however, the u.s. congress banned this after indonesian troops killed hundreds of civilians in east timor", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a killing in east timor"}
{"passage": "1991, however, the u.s. congress banned this after indonesian troops killed hundreds of civilians in east timo", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a ban in 1991"}
{"passage": "saddam hussein controlled iraq through fear, torture and execution", "answer": false, "question": "Was there an execution in new winsdor"}
{"passage": "african immigrants who came ashore thursday in southern spain aboard an overcrowded boat, including several pregnant women and other travelers suffering from hypothermia", "answer": true, "question": "Did the immigration happen on thursday?"}
{"passage": "saddam hussein controlled iraq through fear, torture and execution", "answer": false, "question": "Did the immigration happen on wednesday?"}
{"passage": " u.s. aircraft bombed iraqi tanks holding bridges close to the city", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a bombing close to the city"}
{"passage": "he tried to mend fences by placing a telephone call tuesday to bush ", "answer": false, "question": " Did the call happen on wednesday"}
{"passage": "he was tortured here, along with his two brothers, who were executed", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a torture here"}
{"passage": " here, prisoners were tortured", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a torture here   "}
{"passage": "relatives murdered here", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a murder here"}
{"passage": " he was tortured here, along with his two brothers, who were executed", "answer": true, "question": "Was the execution here    "}
{"passage": " saddam hussein controlled iraq through fear, torture and execution", "answer": true, "question": "Was there fear in iraq"}
{"passage": "the president having flown back to the united states from that meeting in northern ireland in belfast with the british prime minister", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a meeting in northern ireland"}
{"passage": "the president having flown back to the united states from that meeting in northern ireland in belfast with the british prime minister", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a meeting in the united states"}
{"passage": "the president having flown back to the united states from that meeting in northern ireland in belfast with the british prime minister", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a meeting in belfast  "}
{"passage": "war in iraq ", "answer": false, "question": " Was there a war in los angeles  "}
{"passage": "he died there", "answer": false, "question": "Was the death here"}
{"passage": "she was in charge of the iraqi facility that weaponized anthrax", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a weaponization in iraq"}
{"passage": "he is being tried in greece", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a try in greece"}
{"passage": "he is being tried in greece", "answer": false, "question": "Did the try happen in sumatra"}
{"passage": "ocalan, leader of the kurdistan workers party, or pkk, is serving a life sentence in turkey for leading a 15-year insurgency against the country that left 37,000 people dead", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a sentence in turkey"}
{"passage": "ocalan, leader of the kurdistan workers party, or pkk, is serving a life sentence in turkey for leading a 15-year insurgency against the country that left 37,000 people dead ", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a death in turkey"}
{"passage": "less than 24 hours, the u.s. 101st airborne division has driven iraqi fedayeen fighters from the key city of najaf ", "answer": false, "question": " Did the driving happen two days ago"}
{"passage": "the army's 3rd infantry has punched through karbala, meeting only light resistance from the medina republican guard", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a resistance in the gaza strip "}
{"passage": " gulf war 12 years ago", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a war 12 years ago "}
{"passage": "kelly, the us assistant secretary for east asia and pacific affairs, arrived in seoul from beijing friday", "answer": false, "question": " Did the arrival happen on thursday  "}
{"passage": "kelly, the us assistant secretary for east asia and pacific affairs, arrived in seoul from beijing friday", "answer": false, "question": "Was the arrival in beijing"}
{"passage": "kelly, the us assistant secretary for east asia and pacific affairs, arrived in seoul from beijing friday", "answer": true, "question": "Was the arrival in seoul"}
{"passage": "kelly, the us assistant secretary for east asia and pacific affairs, arrived in seoul from beijing friday", "answer": true, "question": " Did the arrival happen on friday"}
{"passage": "1997, she successfully founded the china polar museum foundation", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a founding in 1997  "}
{"passage": "a brooklyn woman who scalded her 4-year-old to death in a bathtub, walked out of court a free woman yesterday sentenced to five years probation", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a sentence yesterday   "}
{"passage": "a couple of hours ago, rescued p.o.w. jessica lynch arrived at the ramstein air base in germany", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an arrival to germany   "}
{"passage": "u.s. and british troops were moving on the strategic southern port city of basra saturday", "answer": false, "question": " Did the moving happen sunday"}
{"passage": "u.s. and british troops were moving on the strategic southern port city of basra saturday", "answer": true, "question": " Did the moving happen saturday"}
{"passage": "battle for basra, an oil hub of some 1.3 million people, was underway by midday, with coalition troops trying to surround iraqi positions", "answer": false, "question": " Was there a battle in sumatra"}
{"passage": "battle for basra, an oil hub of some 1.3 million people, was underway by midday, with coalition troops trying to surround iraqi positions", "answer": false, "question": "Did the battle happen in the evening"}
{"passage": "one day after a massive u.s. aerial bombardment in which more than 300 tomahawk cruise missiles rained down on the capital", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a bombardment in the capital"}
{"passage": "one day after a massive u.s. aerial bombardment in which more than 300 tomahawk cruise missiles rained down on the capital", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a bombardment today "}
{"passage": " two royal navy helicopters over the persian gulf in which all six british crew members and one american were killed", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a killing in the persian gulf"}
{"passage": "saturday morning, american marines and british troops rumbled along the main road from the kuwaiti border to basra", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a rumbling saturday morning  "}
{"passage": "the main road from the kuwaiti border to basra, highway 80, nicknamed the ``highway of death'' during the 1991 gulf war, when u.s. airstrikes wiped out an iraqi military convoy", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a wipeout in bali"}
{"passage": "the main road from the kuwaiti border to basra, highway 80, nicknamed the ``highway of death'' during the 1991 gulf war, when u.s. airstrikes wiped out an iraqi military convoy", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a wipeout in france"}
{"passage": "the main road from the kuwaiti border to basra, highway 80, nicknamed the ``highway of death'' during the 1991 gulf war, when u.s. airstrikes wiped out an iraqi military convoy", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a wipeout in the west bank"}
{"passage": "australian commandos, who have been operating deep in iraq, destroyed a command and control post", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a destruction in iraq"}
{"passage": "australian commandos, who have been operating deep in iraq, destroyed a command and control post and killed a number of soldiers", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a destruction in bali"}
{"passage": "saturday, information minister mohammed saeed al-sahhaf told iraqis that fighting       ", "answer": false, "question": "Did a fighting happen on monday"}
{"passage": "u.s. and british troops had encountered little resistance, even when they seized nearby umm qasr", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a resistance nearby umm qasr  "}
{"passage": "the father, who was piloting the plane, also was rescued, but died late yesterday at the hospital", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a death at the hospital "}
{"passage": "the father, who was piloting the plane, also was rescued, but died late yesterday at the hospital", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a death late yesterday  "}
{"passage": "another a-10 warthog was hit here today", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a hit here "}
{"passage": "one day after a former fbi counterintelligence agent was indicted on charges of gross negligence, his mistress of two decades, katrina leung, was herself indicted on more serious charges of copying and possessing documents relating to the national security of the united states", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a indictment one day after"}
{"passage": "indictment earlier in the week", "answer": false, "question": "Did a indictment happen in 1991"}
{"passage": "leung was hired by the fbi and paid almost $2 million over 20 years", "answer": false, "question": "Did a paid happen for less than 3 months"}
{"passage": "at least ten people have been injured and at least five homes have burned in benton harbor", "answer": false, "question": "Was there an injury in new york "}
{"passage": "new york is facing attempted murder charges after allegedly throwing his baby", "answer": false, "question": " Was there a throwing in paris    "}
{"passage": "fire incident in northern iraq is taking more of a toll on kurdish leaders", "answer": false, "question": " Was there a fire in the west bank   "}
{"passage": " just one day until i hop in the car and head back in time to the loveliest village on the plains", "answer": false, "question": "Did an heading back in time happen today       "}
{"passage": " the coalition took over this base last week", "answer": false, "question": "Did a taking over happen on March 2004"}
{"passage": "that air base that coalition forces have now taken control of near nasiriya  ", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a control in the northern cities of mosul, kirkuk and tikrit, saddam's hometown"}
{"passage": "]yesterday i was up just south of baghdad by 30 miles and we were fighting sa-2s and sa-6s and aaa", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a fighting in baghdad   "}
{"passage": "the air force has just informed us that between this morning and tomorrow morning, it will fly 1,900 sorties into iraq", "answer": false, "question": "Did a flight happen one day"}
{"passage": "explosion there", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a explosion here   "}
{"passage": "last week, if you may recall, there was a strike on afraid in which a number of israeli soldiers killed, that executed by coordinated group of islamic jihad as well as al ak satisfy martyr brigades, and hamas", "answer": false, "question": " Did a strike happen two weeks ago"}
{"passage": " two others who were there did die", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a death here"}
{"passage": " today's suicide bombing in israel", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a suicide in israel"}
{"passage": " today's suicide bombing in israel", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a suicide today  "}
{"passage": " today's suicide bombing in israel", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a bombing in israel"}
{"passage": " today's suicide bombing in israel", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a bombing today  "}
{"passage": "seventy-two hours of that was under constant fire coming at us from both sides of the road", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a fire in the road "}
{"passage": "nighttime raid on the homes of ba'ath party officials and fedayeen militia", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a raid in bali"}
{"passage": "nighttime raid on the homes of ba'ath party officials and fedayeen militia", "answer": false, "question": " Did a raid happen in the morning"}
{"passage": "the 24-year-old gunman went into a best buy store and started firing", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a firing in an hospital"}
{"passage": "the 24-year-old gunman went into a best buy store and started firing", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a firing in a store"}
{"passage": "new york has such strict gun laws - meaning citizens are prohibited from concealing weapons - a gunner can use bag-toting shoppers as target practice   ", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a target practice in new york"}
{"passage": "the mall, perhaps he could have intervened before the suspect began injuring people before he ran out of ammo", "answer": false, "question": "Was there an injuring in the beach  "}
{"passage": "the tobacco industry can sell something with no health benefits for years, get sued", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a selling for years "}
{"passage": "slaughter of 800,000 tutsis and their sympathizers in rwanda in 1994", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a slaughtering in rwanda "}
{"passage": "slaughter of 800,000 tutsis and their sympathizers in rwanda in 1994", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a slaughtering in 1994 "}
{"passage": "rwanda massacres", "answer": true, "question": " Was there massacres in rwanda     "}
{"passage": "the rwandan government which was planning the genocide", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a genocide in rwanda"}
{"passage": "rwandan holocaust", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a holocaust in rwanda"}
{"passage": "rwanda, sent a fax to kofi annan's office, saying he had received evidence from a rwandan government informant that genocide", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a genocide in rwanda   "}
{"passage": "most homosexuals arrested during the nazi era", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an arrest at the nazi era"}
{"passage": "the how ever million were killed in the camps", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a killing in the camps    "}
{"passage": "most homosexuals arrested during the nazi era were imprisoned in normal jails", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a imprisoning in normal jails     "}
{"passage": "san francisco is the setting today for a rally", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a rally in the gulf"}
{"passage": " san francisco is the setting today for a rally     ", "answer": false, "question": "Did the rally happen yesterday"}
{"passage": "los angeles, the international black coalition for peace and justice is sponsoring a rally for peace today", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a rally today "}
{"passage": "los angeles, the international black coalition for peace and justice is sponsoring a rally for peace today", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a rally in los angeles   "}
{"passage": "this is the largest pro-troops demonstration that has ever been in san francisco                                       ", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a demonstration in san franisco   "}
{"passage": "this is the largest pro-troops demonstration that has ever been in san francisco", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a demonstration in new york"}
{"passage": "this is the largest pro-troops demonstration that has ever been in san francisco", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a demonstration in iraq"}
{"passage": "rallies that have been over the last few weeks", "answer": true, "question": "Were there rallies in the last few weeks"}
{"passage": "vietnam war", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a war in bali"}
{"passage": "these civilians especially in the (inaudible) population have been attacked by the iraqi regime themselves", "answer": false, "question": " Was there a attacked in the persian gulf    "}
{"passage": "220 every day die", "answer": true, "question": " Did a death happen saturday "}
{"passage": "obstetricians in california will pay 55, 57, $60,000 in los angeles", "answer": true, "question": "Will there be a payment in los angeles "}
{"passage": "miami, they'll pay $210,000", "answer": false, "question": "Wil the payment be in australia"}
{"passage": "south florida, the latest poll shows that every neurosurgeon has been sued", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a suit in turkey   "}
{"passage": "suits against a neurosurgeon is five in south florida", "answer": true, "question": "Were there suits in south florida    "}
{"passage": "nov. 21 that left six people dead", "answer": false, "question": "Did the death happen september 14"}
{"passage": "september and at the time of this posting, no one has been killed by any one of those weapons", "answer": false, "question": "Did a killing happen one day   "}
{"passage": "convicted of the killings, vang faces life in prison as minnesota", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a conviction in minnesota"}
{"passage": "we stay there for about a year or two, the whole trip could last about three years", "answer": true, "question": "Could the trip last about three years "}
{"passage": "you're on mars, just to talk to people on earth", "answer": false, "question": " Was there a talk in new zeland  "}
{"passage": "300 sorties in a 24-hour period ending today", "answer": false, "question": "Was there the 300 sorties last week  "}
{"passage": "1500 sorties in a 24-hour period ending tomorrow", "answer": false, "question": "Did 1500 sorties happen yesterday   "}
{"passage": "the us is currently engaged in major fighting in fallujah, iraq", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a fighting in fallujah, iraq"}
{"passage": "the us is currently engaged in major fighting in fallujah, iraq", "answer": true, "question": "Is there a fighting currently "}
{"passage": "war in iraq", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a war in paris    "}
{"passage": "war started in iraq", "answer": false, "question": "Was the start in bali  "}
{"passage": "war started in iraq", "answer": false, "question": "Was the start in paris "}
{"passage": "vietnam war", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a war in the gulf "}
{"passage": "he was convicted of hijacking the \"achille lauro\" in 1985", "answer": false, "question": "Does a conviction happen currently              "}
{"passage": "he was convicted of hijacking the \"achille lauro\" in 1985", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a hijacking in 1985   "}
{"passage": "paris hospital last week, after a lot of controversy surrounding his illness and death", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a death last week      "}
{"passage": "romania voted in the last december, ousting the so-called socialist party psd (social-democratic party", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a vote in italy    "}
{"passage": "romania voted in the last december, ousting the so-called socialist party psd (social-democratic party)", "answer": false, "question": " Did the vote happen on march"}
{"passage": "national leaders, pressuring tv stations to lie, associating with old communist ex-president ion iliescu, failed to win in big cities", "answer": false, "question": " Was there a victory in big cities   "}
{"passage": "national leaders, pressuring tv stations to lie, associating with old communist ex-president ion iliescu, failed to win in big cities", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a lying in tv stations   "}
{"passage": "elections in his area", "answer": true, "question": "Was there  elections in his area  "}
{"passage": "psd is building a strategy for the 4 years to come and they are going to elect a leader", "answer": true, "question": " Will there be a strategy for the 4 years to come  "}
{"passage": "psd is building a strategy for the 4 years to come and they are going to elect a leader", "answer": true, "question": " Will there be an election in the 4 years to come   "}
{"passage": " i visited your country in 1994", "answer": true, "question": "Did the visit happen in 1994"}
{"passage": " loss of british lives today ", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a loss today"}
{"passage": "attacking on the ground and calling in air strikes, kurdish fighters and u.s. troops have dislodged stubborn iraqi soldiers at a key bridge in northern iraq", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a attacking in a key bridge in northern iraq  "}
{"passage": "strikes, kurdish fighters and u.s. troops have dislodged stubborn iraqi soldiers at a key bridge in northern iraq ", "answer": false, "question": "Were the a strikes in rwanda   "}
{"passage": "battle going on here", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a battle here        "}
{"passage": "at least three u.s. service members were killed today in an apparent suicide bomb attack at a checkpoint near the haditah dam northwest of baghdad", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a killing in a checkpoint near the haditah dam northwest of baghdad  "}
{"passage": "at least three u.s. service members were killed today in an apparent suicide bomb attack at a checkpoint near the haditah dam northwest of baghdad", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a killing today    "}
{"passage": "today in an apparent suicide bomb attack at a checkpoint near the haditah dam northwest of baghdad", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a suicide in a best buy store   "}
{"passage": " today in an apparent suicide bomb attack at a checkpoint near the haditah dam northwest of baghdad", "answer": false, "question": "Did the suicide happen 12-year ago     "}
{"passage": " at least three u.s. service members were killed today in an apparent suicide bomb attack at a checkpoint near the haditah dam northwest of baghdad", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an attack in a checkpoint near the haditah dam northwest of baghdad    "}
{"passage": " at least three u.s. service members were killed today in an apparent suicide bomb attack at a checkpoint near the haditah dam northwest of baghdad", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an attack today"}
{"passage": "this day, including more than 400 civilians killed", "answer": false, "question": " Did the killing happen last year"}
{"passage": "the iraqis promise an unconventional attack on u.s. troops tonight", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an attack tonight "}
{"passage": " warfare, as in vietnam", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a warfare here in the north"}
{"passage": " marines battling for control of the bridges in the southern city of nasiriyah face stiff resistance from iraqi paramilitary groups today", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a battle in the southern city of nasiriyah "}
{"passage": "marines battling for control of the bridges in the southern city of nasiriyah face stiff resistance from iraqi paramilitary groups today", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a battle today  "}
{"passage": "you are going to fight on the ground", "answer": false, "question": "Will there be a fight on the air"}
{"passage": "you are going to fight on the ground", "answer": true, "question": "Will there be a fight on the ground"}
{"passage": "the giant u.s. carrier constellation is now returning home from the war in iraq", "answer": true, "question": "Is a return happening now"}
{"passage": "this little beautiful boy was born two days after deployment", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a birth two days after deployment"}
{"passage": "he was born on november 4th", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a birth on november 4th    "}
{"passage": "that firm's bankruptcy filing a few days ago", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a bankruptcy a few days ago  "}
{"passage": "a girl that i've hired uh well, i hired her, let's see, about nine years ago", "answer": false, "question": " Did the hiring happen yesterday"}
{"passage": "the youngest person elected president in american history", "answer": true, "question": " Was there an election in america      "}
{"passage": "incidents in colorado springs, colo", "answer": true, "question": "Were there incidents in colorado springs, colo     "}
{"passage": "you pick up at a military surplus store", "answer": false, "question": " Was there a pick up in a pharmacy"}
{"passage": "you pick up at a military surplus store", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a pick up in a military surplus store  "}
{"passage": "homeland security appropriations designated $60 million in fy2004 and $61 million in fy2005 to fund", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a fund in fy2004 "}
{"passage": "homeland security appropriations designated $60 million in fy2004 and $61 million in fy2005 to fund", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a fund in fy2005   "}
{"passage": " i talked to secretary powell this morning", "answer": false, "question": "Did a talk happen last saturday    "}
{"passage": "assassination of lebanon's former prime minister in beirut on monday", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a assassination in the russian leader's native city of saint petersburg   "}
{"passage": "assassination of lebanon's former prime minister in beirut on monday", "answer": false, "question": "Did the assassination happen on tuesday "}
{"passage": "the middle east, one determined to undermine peace talks by supporting militant groups that attack israelis", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an attack in the middle east   "}
{"passage": "brussels on wednesday at a meeting of the clearing house", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a meeting in tokyo       "}
{"passage": "brussels on wednesday at a meeting of the clearing house", "answer": false, "question": "Did the meeting happen on october 2003 "}
{"passage": "the mullahs' terror agent that conducts the proxy attacks against israel that iran cannot afford to do itself openly", "answer": false, "question": "Was there an attack in a mall"}
{"passage": "today, thousands of pro-life crusaders will participate in the march for life in washington d.c", "answer": true, "question": "Will there be a march in washington d.c  "}
{"passage": "today, thousands of pro-life crusaders will participate in the march for life in washington d.c", "answer": true, "question": " Will there be a march today    "}
{"passage": "you vote in the recent us presidential election", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an election in the us"}
{"passage": " you vote in the recent us presidential election", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an election recently"}
{"passage": "conflict in the world", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a conflict in the world   "}
{"passage": "bombardment of baghdad continues tonight and over the past 20 minutes, explosions rocking baghdad, central baghdad southern baghdad, the outskirts of baghdad, and importantly, as the coalition forces, principally u.s. army forces, move against saddam hussein international airport -- which is about ten miles outside the center of baghdad", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a bombardment in cleveland      "}
{"passage": "bombardment of baghdad continues tonight and over the past 20 minutes, explosions rocking baghdad, central baghdad southern baghdad, the outskirts of baghdad, and importantly, as the coalition forces, principally u.s. army forces, move against saddam hussein international airport -- which is about ten miles outside the center of baghdad", "answer": false, "question": "Did the bombardment happen on tuesday"}
{"passage": "bombardment of baghdad continues tonight and over the past 20 minutes, explosions rocking baghdad, central baghdad southern baghdad, the outskirts of baghdad, and importantly, as the coalition forces, principally u.s. army forces, move against saddam hussein international airport -- which is about ten miles outside the center of baghdad", "answer": false, "question": "Did the bombardment happen yesterday"}
{"passage": "tonight and over the past 20 minutes, explosions rocking baghdad, central baghdad southern baghdad, the outskirts of baghdad, and importantly, as the coalition forces, principally u.s. army forces, move against saddam hussein international airport -- which is about ten miles outside the center of baghdad", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a move tonight"}
{"passage": "the missiles that we have become accustomed to striking baghdad and its environs", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a striking in minnesota  "}
{"passage": "baghdad, or whether these flashes now represent artillery barrages as fighting continues to take control of the -- to take control of saddam international airport", "answer": true, "question": "Is there a fighting in baghdad "}
{"passage": "strike on march 19th against the location that the cia military intelligence thought was a place where saddam hussein, perhaps his sons, were  hidden", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a strike in march 19"}
{"passage": "explosions rocking parts of baghdad tonight", "answer": true, "question": " Were there explosions in baghdad"}
{"passage": "explosions rocking parts of baghdad tonight", "answer": true, "question": " Were there explosions tonight "}
{"passage": "southern iraq today, british forces also moving closer to the center of the second largest city in iraq, basra", "answer": false, "question": " Did the move happen a year ago   "}
{"passage": "they captured an iraqi base in an unused factory in the southern suburbs of that city", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a capture in the southern suburbs of that city         "}
{"passage": "fan attack in the last seven months", "answer": true, "question": "Was there an attack in the last seven months "}
{"passage": "a ground-breaking british budget cinema chain launched by the founder of low-cost airline easyjet announced friday that it had finally acquired some films to show -- just a fortnight", "answer": false, "question": "Was the announcement on sunday"}
{"passage": "a ground-breaking british budget cinema chain launched by the founder of low-cost airline easyjet announced friday that it had finally acquired some films to show -- just a fortnight", "answer": false, "question": "  Did an acquisition happen two weeks ago "}
{"passage": "easycinema founder stelios haji-ioannou, who set up easyjet in 1995", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a set up  in 1991"}
{"passage": "easycinema founder stelios haji-ioannou, who set up easyjet in 1995", "answer": true, "question": "Is there a debut on may 23"}
{"passage": "easycinema's first outlet in milton keynes, just north of london, which is due to open its doors on may 23", "answer": true, "question": "Is there a debut in milton keynes, just north of london    "}
{"passage": "american commandos captured a half brother of saddam hussein on thursday", "answer": false, "question": " Did the capture happen later tuesday"}
{"passage": "1979 to 1983, he headed iraq's mukhabarat, or intelligence service, a period when the organization arranged executions of regime opponents in iraq and overseas", "answer": true, "question": " Was there executions in iraq"}
{"passage": "1979 to 1983, he headed iraq's mukhabarat, or intelligence service, a period when the organization arranged executions of regime opponents in iraq and overseas", "answer": true, "question": " Were there executions in 1979"}
{"passage": "1979 to 1983, he headed iraq's mukhabarat, or intelligence service, a period when the organization arranged executions of regime opponents in iraq and overseas", "answer": true, "question": " Were there executions in 1983"}
{"passage": "mosul, where u.s. troops killed 17 people in clashes earlier in the week", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a killing in mosul earlier in the week  "}
{"passage": "mosul, where u.s. troops killed 17 people in clashes earlier in the week", "answer": true, "question": "Were there clashes earlier in the week   "}
{"passage": "mosul, where u.s. troops killed 17 people in clashes earlier in the week", "answer": false, "question": "Was there clashes in its vital oil and natural gas fields in sumatra, borneo and papua "}
{"passage": "clashes on wednesday in tikrit", "answer": true, "question": "Were there clashes in tikrit      "}
{"passage": "clashes on wednesday in tikrit", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a clashes on wednesday  "}
{"passage": " international experts, appalled at the looting of iraqi historical artifacts, met in paris", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a meeting in the concentration camps   "}
{"passage": "barzan ibrahim had been a presidential adviser to saddam's regime since 1998", "answer": false, "question": "Was there an advising in 1979"}
{"passage": "he was a representative to the united nations in geneva from 1989", "answer": true, "question": " Was there a representation in geneva "}
{"passage": "he was a representative to the united nations in geneva from 1989", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a representation in 1989   "}
{"passage": " governor mark warner won the district with similar margins in 2001", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a victory in 1995"}
{"passage": " governor mark warner won the district with similar margins in 2001", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a victory in 2001"}
{"passage": "i am humbled by the support of so many citizens in the 42nd district who are voting with their pocketbooks for a change in leadership", "answer": true, "question": "Was there a support in the 42nd district "}
{"passage": "a second straight night and into this morning, hundreds of people have been rioting in benton harbor", "answer": false, "question": "Was there a riot in irak"}
{"passage": "a second straight night and into this morning, hundreds of people have been rioting in benton harbor", "answer": false, "question": "Did a riot happen last october  "}
{"passage": "a second straight night and into this morning, hundreds of people have been rioting in benton harbor", "answer": false, "question": "Did a riot happen earlier in the week"}
{"passage": "14 senior managing directors under a streamlined management system set to be introduced after a shareholders' meeting in june", "answer": true, "question": "Is there a meeting in june  "}
{"question": "Was there a demonstration in the middle east", "answer": false, "passage": "fallujah where there was a shootout between u.s. troops and iraqies who had been demonstrating there"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in texas", "answer": true, "passage": "february when the space shuttle columbia disintegrated over texas, killing all seven crew members"}
{"question": "Was there a death in the united\nstates", "answer": true, "passage": "the united states, 284 people died last year from the west nile virus while 36,000 people die every year"}
{"question": "Was there a trip less than two-days ago", "answer": true, "passage": "president bush returning to the united states from his summit in northern ireland in belfast with british prime minister tony blair, the president back on american soil after a quick two-day trip, less than two-day trip"}
{"question": "Is there an election next year", "answer": true, "passage": "re-electing president bush and dick cheney next year"}
{"question": "Was there an ambush in latifiya", "answer": true, "passage": "deputy governor of diyala along with several council members from ba'quba were ambushed and killed in latifiya"}
{"question": "Was the war in fla", "answer": false, "passage": "war in iraq"}
{"question": "Was the bombing in the supermarket", "answer": false, "passage": "ba'asyir, 64, was arrested on preliminary charges of involvement in a series of church bombings on the eve of the 2000 christmas"}
{"question": "Was there a death last week", "answer": true, "passage": "plo leader yasser arafat died in a paris hospital last week"}
{"question": "Was there a death last week", "answer": true, "passage": "paris hospital last week, after a lot of controversy surrounding his illness and death"}
{"question": "Was there a fighting in new zealand", "answer": false, "passage": "days of fierce fighting that shut down the city of umm qasr"}
{"question": "Was there a conviction in 1989", "answer": true, "passage": "indonesia, where the last execution was carried out in may 2001 of two men convicted of a murder in 1989"}
{"question": "Were there talks on wednesday", "answer": true, "passage": "wednesday stressed qatar's role in the middle east peace process during talks with his qatari counterpart sheikh hamad bin jassem bin jabr al-thani in paris"}
{"question": "Was there an overthrow in palestine", "answer": true, "passage": "arafat hadn't been i don't know if he's -- directly -- been linked to hamas' acts,  uh,  but he was put in a -- pretty -- sticky situation having to negotiate -- the militants of -- palestine -- the international leaders -- and if it if hara- arafat hadn't -- somehow appeased -- the hamas groups or the palestinian militants,  then -- he would've been kicked out,  overthrown"}
{"question": "Was there a payment in coral springs", "answer": false, "passage": "colorado judge ordered two teen-age girls to pay about $900 for the distress a neighbor"}
{"question": "Was there a threat in falluja", "answer": false, "passage": "these battered buildings hold a deadly threat to british forces in iraq"}
{"question": "Was there a two day trip", "answer": true, "passage": "president bush returning to the united states from his summit in northern ireland in belfast with british prime minister tony blair, the president back on american soil after a quick two-day trip"}
{"question": "Did the suit happen lin june", "answer": false, "passage": "anne-marie sued crichton for divorce in september"}
{"question": "Did the attack happen seven years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "four u.s. army soldiers were killed when a suicide bomber attacked a military checkpoint today in najaf"}
{"question": "Was there an attack last year", "answer": true, "passage": "last year, giuliani said nathan gave him ``tremendous emotional support'' through his treatment for prostate cancer and as he led the city during the aftermath of the sept. 11 terrorist attack on the world trade center"}
{"question": "Was the conviction in sweden", "answer": false, "passage": "indonesia to spare the lives of convicted drug offenders"}
{"question": "Was there an invasion in fairfax\ncounty", "answer": false, "passage": "iraq destroyed all its weapons of mass destruction. the united states and britain claim he's lying, and have assembled a quarter-million troops around iraq for a possible invasion"}
{"question": "Was there an accusation in this\ncountry", "answer": true, "passage": "he is accused of attempting to ignite a dirty bomb in this country"}
{"question": "were supplies brought to iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "bring supplies to iraqi civilians had been on hold for days"}
{"question": "Were they flown out yesterday", "answer": false, "passage": "here this morning and we took about 12 or 13 prisoners, three or four enemy were injured and they've now been flown out"}
{"question": "Was there a trial lasting 2 1/2-year", "answer": true, "passage": "the judge refusing to recuse himself during basson's 2 1/2-year trial"}
{"question": "Was there a war in baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "in baghdad, they were all doing the most natural thing during war"}
{"question": "Did the trip happen tuesday", "answer": false, "passage": "sunday to brief south korean officials on their northern trip"}
{"question": "Did the call happen april 14, 2009", "answer": false, "passage": "the btk killer called up a police dispatcher june 2018"}
{"question": "Did the prosecution happen months ago", "answer": false, "passage": "this month o'brien narrowly escaped prosecution over his handling of sexual abuse allegations against priests"}
{"question": "Was there a trial in fl", "answer": true, "passage": "her back to fl for trial on the fta charge"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in a muslim nation", "answer": true, "passage": "the most powerful nation on earth invades and occupies a muslim nation and kills tens of thousands of people"}
{"question": "Was there a enter each year", "answer": true, "passage": "tens of thousands of destitute africans try to enter spain illegally each year"}
{"question": "Was there a campaign in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "us-led campaign in iraq"}
{"question": "Did he helicopter earlier", "answer": false, "passage": "later, he's supposed to helicopter to jericho"}
{"question": "Was there a fight in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "troops to fight in the war on terror in afghanistan and alongside u.s. and british forces in iraq"}
{"question": "Was there a seven-month journey", "answer": true, "passage": "the mars express on its way on a seven-month journey to the red planet, contains really two spacecraft"}
{"question": "Was there a divorce in los angeles", "answer": true, "passage": "hunter, 34, filed for divorce in los angeles superior court, citing irreconcilable differences with the 58-year-old rock star to whom she has been married for nearly 13 years"}
{"question": "Did the killing happen 3 years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "almost exactly a year ago, march 27, at the park hotel during passover, 29 people killed"}
{"question": "Did the giving happen last week", "answer": false, "passage": "we met, early 2004 and that was when i gave him"}
{"question": "Was something secured in basra", "answer": true, "passage": "american units advancing west of basra have already secured"}
{"question": "Was there a conviction in kut", "answer": false, "passage": "malaysia's second highest court on friday rejected an appeal by jailed former deputy prime minister anwar ibrahim against his conviction and nine-year prison sentence for sodomy"}
{"question": "Was there fighting in fallujah, iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "the us is currently engaged in major fighting in fallujah, iraq"}
{"question": "Did the airstrike happen the early 90's", "answer": false, "passage": "apache helicopter airstrike that occurred within the past hour or so, we're now told by palestinians, three people died, 33 others were wounded, six"}
{"question": "Was there a invasion in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "u.s.-led invasion of iraq that began march 20"}
{"question": "did she serve 6 months", "answer": true, "passage": "az troubles again in 2004, she serves 6 months , then the day before she is to be released"}
{"question": "Was the killing in the u.s", "answer": false, "passage": "almost exactly a year ago in madrid, march 27, at the park hotel during passover, 29 people killed"}
{"question": "Was there a bombing in israel", "answer": true, "passage": "today's suicide bombing in israel"}
{"question": "Was there a explosion in byrds creek, richland county", "answer": false, "passage": "explosions rock baghdad after dark"}
{"question": "Did the hellicopter go down in june", "answer": false, "passage": "march 24th, after their apache helicopter went down in iraqi territory"}
{"question": "Was there a firefight in the center of baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "marines involved in a firefight in the center of baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a war 1994", "answer": true, "passage": "1994 civil war in rwanda, where government-led militia slaughtered an estimated 800,000 opposition, and opposition sympathizers in about 100 days"}
{"question": "Did a attacked happen on tuesday", "answer": false, "passage": "a group of 25 to 30 armed men wednesday attacked a house belonging to a village quack doctor in tultuli, 60 kilometers (38 miles) south of tripuras state capital agartala"}
{"question": "Was there a shooting in the west bank", "answer": true, "passage": "israeli troops shot and killed a 16-year-old palestinian boy and critically injured two children, ages 7 and 9, during conflicts in the west bank that erupted tuesday"}
{"question": "Was there fighting today", "answer": true, "passage": "today's fighting in baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a sale a few months ago", "answer": true, "passage": "sold oconer the rifle a few months ago"}
{"question": "Did the election happen in 2007", "answer": false, "passage": "1996, he was elected to the palestinian legislative council"}
{"question": "Was there a transfer in february 2002", "answer": true, "passage": "toefting transferred to bolton in february 2002"}
{"question": "Was there tax in north carolina", "answer": true, "passage": "taxes given to north carolina by smokers adds up to more than 61 cents"}
{"question": "Was there lupus in baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "baghdad has had sporadic episodes of lupus"}
{"question": "Did the proposal happen april 9th", "answer": false, "passage": "giuliani, 58, proposed to nathan, a former nurse, during a november business trip to paris        _  five months after he finalized his divorce from donna hanover after 20 years of marriage"}
{"question": "Was there a killing mid-april", "answer": true, "passage": "palestinian cameramen, shot and killed by an israeli soldier on the west bank in mid-april"}
{"question": "Was the election in mexico", "answer": false, "passage": "electoral arithmetic: the states where lincoln got an abolute majority of the popular vote (i.e., all the free states except oregon, california, and new jersey) were sufficient to bring him a majority in the electoral college"}
{"question": "Is the meeting in 2010", "answer": false, "passage": "i offered to attend the board meeting in october 2003"}
{"question": "Was the election in thailand", "answer": false, "passage": "recent us presidential election"}
{"question": "Was there a forum in houston", "answer": true, "passage": "houston center, accountable for causing registrations into the landmark forum"}
{"question": "Was there a assassination in illinois", "answer": false, "passage": "zarqawi planned the assassination of u.s. diplomat lawrence foley in jordan last october"}
{"question": "Was there a pounding in jordan", "answer": false, "passage": "pounded baghdad at dawn"}
{"question": "Was the police take him to the hospital", "answer": true, "passage": "a short time later, two police officers showed up and told me they had to take him back to the hospital"}
{"question": "Was there a attack in a public\nplace", "answer": true, "passage": "who is under attack in a public place"}
{"question": "Were the attacks in oklahoma\ncity", "answer": false, "passage": "attacks in gaza"}
{"question": "Was laos taken overnight", "answer": true, "passage": "laos will be taken overnight"}
{"question": "Was there a replacement earlier in the season", "answer": true, "passage": "our starter since replacing rix earlier in the season"}
{"question": "Was the trial in indochina", "answer": false, "passage": "trial in malaysia a couple months into it"}
{"question": "Did the bombing happen in 1990", "answer": false, "passage": "he pleaded not guilty to bombing a birmingham women's clinic in 1998"}
{"question": "Was there a attacks the\nfall of 2001", "answer": true, "passage": "anthrax attacks in the fall of 2001"}
{"question": "Was he shot in israel", "answer": false, "passage": "palestinian cameramen, shot and killed by an israeli soldier on the west bank of iran in mid-april"}
{"question": "Was there a shot in the mediterranean", "answer": true, "passage": "the terrorists shot him and pushed him over the side of the ship into the mediterranean"}
{"question": "Was there a war in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "war, cnn's gary tuchman is joining us now live from an air base not far from iraq"}
{"question": "Did a battle happen already", "answer": false, "passage": "battle is about to begin, maybe only days from now"}
{"question": "Was there a defeat in kut", "answer": true, "passage": "u.s.-led forces were able to press farther north after defeating iraqi republican guard units at karbala and kut"}
{"question": "Was there a stay in jail", "answer": true, "passage": "they will stay in jail until the trial starts in roughly 18 months"}
{"question": "Did the meeting happen a week ago", "answer": false, "passage": "president bush will leave france in a few hour's time after a second meeting face-to-face in private with french president jacque chirac today"}
{"question": "Was there a sentence in central punjab province", "answer": true, "passage": "a pakistani court in central punjab province has sentenced a christian man to life imprisonment for a blasphemy"}
{"question": "Was the arrest on saturday", "answer": true, "passage": "some 70 people were arrested saturday as demonstrators clashed with police at the end of a major peace rally here"}
{"question": "Was there a talks last\nmonth", "answer": false, "passage": "north korea called off two working-level talks with south korea last month"}
{"question": "Was there a trial january", "answer": true, "passage": "luster skipped bail during his trial in january for raping and drugging three women"}
{"question": "Was there a bombings in egypt", "answer": false, "passage": "bombings in saudi arabia"}
{"question": "Was there a death in a\nparis hospital", "answer": true, "passage": "plo leader yasser arafat died in a paris hospital last week"}
{"question": "Were people injured in israel", "answer": true, "passage": "dozens were injured today in the first suicide bombing in israel"}
{"question": "Did he take over the ministry on april 21", "answer": false, "passage": "tvrdik, who took over the defense ministry in may 2001"}
{"question": "Was there a summit in france", "answer": true, "passage": "the g-8 summit in france"}
{"question": "Was the war in europe", "answer": false, "passage": "iran, hope -- and buzz writes no one wants to see a war"}
{"question": "Was there a charge on wednesday", "answer": true, "passage": "stewart was charged by federal authorities wednesday"}
{"question": "Was there a protest in the atlanta headquarters", "answer": true, "passage": "others at the atlanta headquarters protested"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in a park", "answer": true, "passage": "banks was convicted of shooting and killing a 16-year-old at a park in 1980"}
{"question": "Was the hunter born in new zealand", "answer": true, "passage": "new zealand-born hunter"}
{"question": "Were they charged in Ghana", "answer": false, "passage": "50 executives now charged in america"}
{"question": "Was there an appeal in indonesia", "answer": true, "passage": "indonesia will delay the execution of six convicts including an indian on death row after five of them appealed to the supreme court"}
{"question": "Was the invasion into agartala", "answer": false, "passage": "the most powerful nation on earth invades and occupies a muslim nation"}
{"question": "Was the meeting in saudi arabia", "answer": false, "passage": "iranian senior officials were meeting there at home, possibly including saddam hussein and his sons"}
{"question": "Did a missions happen four years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "the european space agency both launch missions to mars this month sending rovers and ashters"}
{"question": "Will they tie the knot tonight", "answer": true, "passage": "the couple is preparing to tie the knot at gracie mansion in new york tonight"}
{"question": "Did the shooting happen almost three-years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "yesterday, 164 days after the expiration of the federal \"assault weapons\" ban some lunatic opened fire with an ak-47 outside a texas courthouse"}
{"question": "Did they succeed yugoslavia a year ago", "answer": false, "passage": "become a deputy in the parliament of serbia and montenegro, the country that last month succeeded yugoslavia"}
{"question": "Did the death happen in june", "answer": false, "passage": "265 people died in the november 2001"}
{"question": "Was the slaughter mentioned on cnn", "answer": false, "passage": "auswitch on the bbc breakfast programme, they referred to the slaughter of thousands of jews and others"}
{"question": "Did the vacation happen in may", "answer": false, "passage": "the premier of the western canadian province of british columbia pleaded no contest to driving drunk during a hawaiian vacation in january"}
{"question": "Was there a build in sydney", "answer": true, "passage": "sydney and we are going to build a monster"}
{"question": "Was there a demonstration against israeli", "answer": true, "passage": "demonstrations are routinely held against israel all over the world"}
{"question": "Was there a hit in the iraqi capital", "answer": true, "passage": "the nine-story security headquarters in the iraqi capital took a direct hit, strewing bricks, masonry and glass across the street in the al-salhiya neighborhood of central baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a conference today", "answer": true, "passage": "he reiterated today in a press conference in baghdad"}
{"question": "Did the q&a happen last week", "answer": false, "passage": "defense secretary donald rumsfeld took part in a q&a with the troops today"}
{"question": "Was the war in kirkuk", "answer": false, "passage": "iraq war, at least 130 iraqi civilians have been reportedly killed since the war"}
{"question": "Was there a genocide in rwanda", "answer": true, "passage": "1994 genocide in rwanda"}
{"question": "Was the killing in baghdad", "answer": false, "passage": "he was killed in action in iraq"}
{"question": "Does he run a software company", "answer": false, "passage": "i ran a software company for a few years and then started my own tyre company"}
{"question": "Did a clashing happen today", "answer": false, "passage": "a week ago, protesters have been clashing with police and backers of the clerical regime in tehran"}
{"question": "Did a talking to happen roughly 18\nmonths ago", "answer": false, "passage": "here in the united states this weekend just as they did last weekend, anti-war protesters talking to fellow people"}
{"question": "Did the attacks happen july 2002", "answer": false, "passage": "1987, after attacks on kuwaiti oil tankers"}
{"question": "Was there a hit in mosul", "answer": true, "passage": "bombers have also hit targets in the northern cities of mosul, kirkuk and tikrit, saddam's hometown"}
{"question": "Was the executions in indonesia", "answer": false, "passage": "a makeshift morgue points to mass executions by the iraqi regime"}
{"question": "Was the hearing in washington, d.c", "answer": false, "passage": "an oklahoma city judge has ruled prosecutors presented enough evidence at a preliminary hearing to try nichols on murder"}
{"question": "Did the election happen two-day ago", "answer": false, "passage": "elected lt. gov, instead of wilder, all those years ago"}
{"question": "Did the meet already happen", "answer": false, "passage": "they are scheduled to meet next in the russian leader's native city of saint petersburg in late may"}
{"question": "Was there a deaths in 27 countries", "answer": true, "passage": "deaths in 27 countries"}
{"question": "Did the summit happen june 20", "answer": false, "passage": "g-8 meeting, us-canada (relations) and other international issues of concern,\" bush spokesman ari fleischer said days before the june 1-3 summit, to be held in france"}
{"question": "Was the fighting in fallujah, iraq", "answer": false, "passage": "fighting in this area of malaysia"}
{"question": "Was the meeting in the balkans", "answer": false, "passage": "president bush will leave france in a few hour's time after a second meeting face-to-face in private with french president jacque chirac today"}
{"question": "Was the meeting in america", "answer": false, "passage": "they are scheduled to meet next in the russian leader's native city of saint petersburg in late may"}
{"question": "Did the creditors take happen in 1992", "answer": false, "passage": "the creditors attempt to that take money from him in 2005"}
{"question": "were the sales in the 1950s", "answer": false, "passage": "the united states quickly became the southeast asian country's main weapons supplier, and annual arms sales peaked at us$400 million in the 1980s"}
{"question": "Was there a founding in  1937", "answer": true, "passage": "kiichiro toyoda founded the automaker in 1937"}
{"question": "Was there a torture in north carolina", "answer": false, "passage": "torture that have grippedded the country of france since 1998"}
{"question": "Was there a wounding in a church", "answer": false, "passage": "a lone gunman opened fire with an assault rifle sunday inside a crowded mall in upstate new york, wounding one person"}
{"question": "Was there a fight in australia", "answer": false, "passage": "fight on those avenues in that sprawling city of baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a negotiations april 23", "answer": true, "passage": "negotiations between washington and pyongyang on their nuclear dispute have been set for april 23 in bejing"}
{"question": "Was there a shooting shortly after\n3 p.m.", "answer": true, "passage": "the gunman began shooting inside the hudson valley mall shortly after 3 p.m. in kingston, nearly 90 miles north of new york city"}
{"question": "Was there a attack in the outskirts of riyadh", "answer": false, "passage": "netanya, including the deadliest suicide bombing ever in israel almost exactly a year ago, march 27, at the park hotel during passover, 29 people killed in that attack"}
{"question": "Was there a war lasting 100 days", "answer": true, "passage": "1994 civil war in rwanda, where government-led militia slaughtered an estimated 800,000 opposition, and opposition sympathizers in about 100 days"}
{"question": "Was there a hired about nine years ago", "answer": true, "passage": "hired her, let's see, about nine years ago"}
{"question": "is the smash through happening now", "answer": false, "passage": "early saturday, more units were waiting in kuwait to smash through any iraqi"}
{"question": "Was there a attack in the bridge in San jose", "answer": false, "passage": "british forces continue their attack on targets around basra"}
{"question": "Was there a war in turkey", "answer": false, "passage": "war in china, she"}
{"question": "Was he released earlier this year", "answer": true, "passage": "treason filed an appeal wednesday in an effort to overturn the guilty verdict against his client, who was released on parole earlier this year"}
{"question": "Was there a take over may 2001", "answer": true, "passage": "tvrdik, who took over the defense ministry in may 2001"}
{"question": "Was there a wounding in atlanta-area", "answer": false, "passage": "a village near the west bank city of nablus on tuesday, israeli troops opened fire on youths throwing stones, hitting a 9-year-old palestinian boy in the head and critically wounding him, and hitting two 12-year-old boys in the legs, lightly wounding them"}
{"question": "Was there a attack sept. 11", "answer": true, "passage": "last year, giuliani said nathan gave him ``tremendous emotional support'' through his treatment for prostate cancer and as he led the city during the aftermath of the sept. 11 terrorist attack on the world trade center"}
{"question": "is there a meet next week", "answer": true, "passage": "both sides will meet with president bush when he arrives in the mideast next week"}
{"question": "Were there attacks in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "islamic jihad militants are already inside iraq to carry out attacks against u.s. and british forces"}
{"question": "Did the launch happen 40 days ago", "answer": false, "passage": "the second rover, named opportunity, will be launched later this month, and both are expected to arrive at mars in january"}
{"question": "Was there a wounding on tuesday", "answer": true, "passage": "114 people were wounded in tuesday's southern philippines airport"}
{"question": "Did the marching happen yesterday", "answer": false, "passage": "americans this weekend are marching"}
{"question": "Was there a war before march 17", "answer": true, "passage": "end the war by march 17"}
{"question": "Was the arrest in san fransisco", "answer": false, "passage": "24-year-old enrique alvarez, also known as david cruz, was arrested monday in san jose"}
{"question": "Was there a cross april 9th", "answer": true, "passage": "april 9th, about 130 journalists from around the world including myself and a couple of reporters, we were going to try to cross the border because we were all desperate to get into iraq, two days after the saddam statue fell"}
{"question": "Were they sent over the past weekend", "answer": false, "passage": "we sent in one of our companies of about 100 men in here this morning"}
{"question": "Was there an execution in 1979", "answer": true, "passage": "1979 to 1983, he headed iraq's mukhabarat, or intelligence service, a period when the organization arranged executions of regime opponents in iraq and overseas"}
{"question": "Was there a throwing in a village near the west bank city of nablus", "answer": true, "passage": "a village near the west bank city of nablus on tuesday, israeli troops opened fire on youths throwing stones"}
{"question": "Was there a emerge in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "a civilian government emerge in iraq, a democratically elected one, that there'd be more cooperation from the international community, on both the peacekeeping side as well as the political restructuring that's necessary in iraq"}
{"question": "Did a leave happen overnight", "answer": false, "passage": "saddam 48 hours to leave iraq"}
{"question": "Did the conversation happen 10:00 a.m.", "answer": false, "passage": "the 19-year-old army private spoke to her parents yesterday night pie phone from a hospital in germany"}
{"question": "Was there a war in iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "war in iraq to fears that it will lose oil contracts that were sealed with the now-toppled regime of saddam hussein"}
{"question": "Was there a battle in the town", "answer": true, "passage": "reports gone to the town to cover the battles"}
{"question": "Was there a firing in the market", "answer": false, "passage": "here in the north camps, iraqi tanks and guns are still firing"}
{"question": "Did the taking to happen in the past", "answer": false, "passage": "here in the united states this weekend just as they did last weekend, anti-war protesters taking to"}
{"question": "Did the conference happen on friday", "answer": false, "passage": "conference hoon hosted wednesday with representatives from 16 countries, mostly nato members"}
{"question": "Was there a bombing friday", "answer": true, "passage": "bombing campaign unleashed friday on baghdad"}
{"question": "Was the fight in birmingham", "answer": false, "passage": "troops to fight in the war on terror in afghanistan"}
{"question": "Was th killing in texas", "answer": false, "passage": "the last person killed in the washington, d.c. sniper attacks"}
{"question": "Was there a appeal friday", "answer": true, "passage": "malaysia's second highest court on friday rejected an appeal by jailed former deputy prime minister anwar ibrahim against his conviction and nine-year prison sentence for sodomy"}
{"question": "Is there a war", "answer": true, "passage": "two weeks after the air war began, there is no let-up and no effective response from the iraqis"}
{"question": "Was there a striking in baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "the large 2,000 pound jdam bombs that have been striking targets sclected by the coalition in baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a blast in the cafe", "answer": true, "passage": "how many people were in the cafe at the time of the blast"}
{"question": "Was there death near the iraq-kuwait\nborder", "answer": false, "passage": "china, the country where sars originated, has been the hardest hit, with thousands of cases and more than 100 deaths"}
{"question": "Did the meeting happen last month", "answer": false, "passage": "today's meeting in paris, where france, russia and germany"}
{"question": "Do you always go back to prison", "answer": false, "passage": "you can go back to prison for violating the conditions of your parole, for a period of time"}
{"question": "Was the war in concentration camps", "answer": false, "passage": "the 17,000-strong farc, the largest guerrilla force in colombia, has been fighting a war against the government for more than 40 years"}
{"question": "Was there a turbulence in lebanon", "answer": true, "passage": "new turbulence in lebanon"}
{"question": "Was the killing in cuba", "answer": false, "passage": "abc news producer david kaplan was killed by sniper fire in the balkans in 1992"}
{"question": "Was there a killing this morning", "answer": true, "passage": "pennsylvania a student fatally shot a principal before killing himself this morning"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in california", "answer": true, "passage": "the first person to be (()) um -- uh -- killed for a crime in california in like, thirty five years or something"}
{"question": "Did the killing happen on sunday", "answer": false, "passage": "at least 19 people were killed and 114 people were wounded in tuesday's southern philippines airport"}
{"question": "Did the crossing happen today", "answer": false, "passage": "last saturday denied turkish troops had crossed into iraq"}
{"question": "Was there a hit today", "answer": true, "passage": "three planes hit today"}
{"question": "Did he take office on february 27", "answer": true, "passage": "he took office as israel's foreign minister on february 27"}
{"question": "Did the call happen five days ago", "answer": false, "passage": "i plan to call her this morning"}
{"question": "Was there a conflict in the peninsula", "answer": true, "passage": "conflict on the peninsula"}
{"question": "Was there a marriage for a year", "answer": true, "passage": "they were married that long, maybe a year"}
{"question": "Was there a fighting in baghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "baghdad because such fighting"}
{"question": "Did they go back back happen 1942", "answer": false, "passage": "u.n. inspectors went back to iraq for the first time in four years in late november 2018 and discovered no weapons of mass destruction"}
{"question": "Was there a wedding this weekend", "answer": true, "passage": "their brother's wedding this weekend"}
{"question": "Was there a release in january", "answer": true, "passage": "pasko, whose sentence included time served, was released in january"}
{"question": "Did the action happen in march 2016", "answer": false, "passage": "action trends during 2004"}
{"question": "Was there an explosion there", "answer": true, "passage": "explosion there and we understand that several people"}
{"question": "Did the meet happenthis morning", "answer": false, "passage": "leaders of erdogan's justice and development party met tuesday evening"}
{"question": "Was the sentence in france", "answer": false, "passage": "sam waksal, sentenced, 10:00 a.m., local time here in new york"}
{"question": "Was the raid in the sea", "answer": false, "passage": "u.s. forces in baghdad are staging spot raids around that city"}
{"question": "Was there a summit in saint petersburg", "answer": true, "passage": "saint petersburg summit"}
{"question": "Did the fire happen 5 years ago", "answer": false, "passage": "a village near the west bank city of nablus on tuesday, israeli troops opened fire on youths throwing stones"}
{"question": "Was there a overthrew in israel", "answer": false, "passage": "iran, the reason that you had ayatollah khomeini in power is he overthrew the shah"}
{"question": "Was the bombing in colorado springs", "answer": false, "passage": "terrorist attacks here in netanya, including the deadliest suicide bombing ever in israel almost exactly a year ago, march 27, at the park hotel during passover"}
{"question": "Was there an elimination in those citys", "answer": true, "passage": "the three assets the intel which they need to close with and eliminate final remnants of the regime in those citys"}
{"question": "Was something taken in the outskirts of\nbaghdad", "answer": true, "passage": "the army and coalition forces do take control of saddam hussein international airport, just on the outskirts of baghdad"}
{"question": "Was there a birth early saturday", "answer": true, "passage": "a baby boy early saturday, eliminating any chance that the los angeles lakers center might skip a playoff game to witness the birth"}
{"question": "Was the wounding in bagdad airport", "answer": false, "passage": "a village near the west bank city of nablus on tuesday, israeli troops opened fire on youths throwing stones, hitting a 9-year-old palestinian boy in the head and critically wounding him"}
{"question": "Did the hearings happen in june", "answer": false, "passage": "march 17, 2003 -- with coleman's credibility under serious attack, new hearings for the tulia defendants"}
{"question": "Was there a protest sunday", "answer": true, "passage": "some 2,500 mainly university students formed a human chain in japanese characters spelling out \"no war\" in osaka on sunday to protest"}
{"question": "Was there a uprising for 33-month", "answer": true, "passage": "33-month palestinian uprising as israel removed all major checkpoints in the coastal territory, a palestinian"}
{"question": "Did a pardon happen thursday", "answer": false, "passage": "on friday, after 40 days in prison, jordan's king abdullah ii pardoned the former legislator known for her harsh criticism of the state"}
{"question": "Was there a execution in the country", "answer": false, "passage": "no blasphemy convict has ever been executed in the country"}
{"question": "Was there a life term serving in ohio", "answer": false, "passage": "the oklahoma city bombing conspirator is already serving a life term in federal prison"}
{"question": "Was there a sale december 2001", "answer": true, "passage": "11-billion-dollar sale of usa interactive's film and television operations to the french media company in december 2001"}
{"question": "Was there a phone call yesterday", "answer": true, "passage": "i was on the phone with michelle williams yesterday"}
{"question": "Did the blasts happen a week ago", "answer": false, "passage": "blasts to the south as well so it appears that this bombing in this area continues and we have really seen the most intense bombing of the war in this area in the last 24 hours"}
{"question": "Was there a founding in the early 1970's", "answer": true, "passage": "the national carousel association was founded in the early 1970's by a group of art historians and collectors, including frederick fried, author of the 1964 book \"a pictorial history of the carousel\" that single-handedly gave the classic hand-carved wooden carousel the respect and appreciation it deserved"}
{"question": "Was there a talks in camp david", "answer": true, "passage": "camp david talks"}
{"question": "Was the gathering in karbala", "answer": false, "passage": "several thousand demonstrators also gathered outside the white house in washington"}
{"question": "Was there a bombing in oklahoma city", "answer": true, "passage": "the oklahoma city bombing conspirator"}
{"question": "Is there a closing now", "answer": true, "passage": "now is that the emergency rooms are closing, trauma centers are closing"}
{"question": "Was the murder in the greater washington area", "answer": false, "passage": "oklahoma judge has ruled that terry nichols will indeed stand trial in that state court on 160 counts of first-degree murder"}
{"question": "Did the first loan happen in 1971", "answer": false, "passage": "the world bank first offered the loan in 1999"}
{"question": "Was there an attack in netanya", "answer": true, "passage": "attacks here in netanya"}
{"question": "Was there an arrival sunday", "answer": true, "passage": "who also arrived in seoul on sunday for a two-day"}
{"question": "Was there a bombing in mosul", "answer": true, "passage": "mosul bombing"}
{"question": "Was there a meeting thursday", "answer": true, "passage": "meeting would take place thursday"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in 1998", "answer": true, "passage": "killings and rapes and torture that have grippedded the country since 1998"}
{"question": "Was the conflict in dallas, usa", "answer": false, "passage": "israeli troops shot and killed a 16-year-old palestinian boy and critically injured two children, ages 7 and 9, during conflicts in the west bank that erupted tuesday"}
{"question": "Is the summit in the usa", "answer": false, "passage": "summit with u.s. president george w. bush could take place as early as next week in jordan"}
{"question": "Did they leave in january", "answer": true, "passage": "these soldiers were set to leave in january"}
{"question": "Was there a execution in indonesia", "answer": true, "passage": "indonesia will delay the execution of six convicts including an indian on death row"}
{"question": "Was there a murder charge", "answer": true, "passage": "now, willie williams, the little girl's father is charged with attempted murder"}
{"question": "Was he police chief in new york", "answer": true, "passage": "he used to be the chief of police of new york"}
{"question": "Was there a bombardment in the rolling hills of northern iraq", "answer": true, "passage": "the rolling hills of northern iraq, coalition air strikes targeted iraqi positions today in what's been called a ferocious bombardment"}
{"question": "Was the war in karbala", "answer": false, "passage": "postwar iraq"}
{"question": "Did the cross happen between alaska and singapore", "answer": false, "passage": "each day about 90,000 people cross the border between malaysia and singapore"}
{"question": "Was the war in america", "answer": false, "passage": "iraq just before the war began on march 20"}
{"question": "Was there a wounding on tuesday", "answer": true, "passage": "israeli soldiers shot and killed a 16-year-old palestinian boy and wounded a 7-year-old boy after opening fire at stone throwers in the tulkarem refugee camp in the west bank on tuesday"}
{"question": "Was there an attack in central baghdad", "answer": false, "passage": "indonesia uses short-range rapier missiles purchased 30 years ago to protect its vital oil and natural gas fields in sumatra, borneo and papua from air attack"}
{"question": "Did they arrive in march", "answer": false, "passage": "both will arrive at mars in january"}
{"question": "Did the arrest happen on wednesday", "answer": false, "passage": "24-year-old enrique alvarez, also known as david cruz, was arrested monday in san jose"}
{"question": "Was there a killing in india", "answer": true, "passage": "india's has been reeling under a heatwave since mid-may which has killed 1,403 people"}
{"question": "Was there a summit in camp david", "answer": true, "passage": "their first war summit on march 27 at camp david,  blair and bush"}
{"question": "are there elections in january", "answer": true, "passage": "elections scheduled for january"}
{"question": "Was the gun fire in a church", "answer": false, "passage": "a lone gunman opened fire with an assault rifle sunday inside a crowded mall in upstate new york, wounding one person"}
{"question": "Did the lander arrive in 1999", "answer": true, "passage": "in 1999 the mars polar lander arrived"}
{"question": "Was the laser used in thailand", "answer": false, "passage": "they had planned to use the laser against tokyo policemen"}
{"question": "Was there a call at 2:15", "answer": true, "passage": "2:15 the next morning, i received a call from the night shift supervisor who told me my friend had been \"verbally abusive and aggressive\" and would i come over and talk to him"}
{"question": "Was there an invasion in the 1980s", "answer": true, "passage": "1980-1988, which when saddam launched a land/ air invasion of iran"}
